Hello?
I found out who's been adding fuel
to the fire against you online.
I'm listening.
It's some guy named Takashina.
He's from the Tohyama Clinic.
Used to be a detective.
But the whole thing is weird, 'cause,
I mean, you've been working there
for a while now, right?
So what exactly is the point
of stirring all this up against you now?
I see.
I'll call you later.
You're serious?
Sorry, I refuse to believe that.
Why?
Apparently, Lily made tonight's dessert
by watching a video tutorial.
From the Moenon Channel.
Is that so?
Cut me some slack, would you?
It's a good one.
It's authentic.
- Was it about your mother?
- What?
- Your call.
- Oh.
Yes, it was.
Turns out my mother finished rehab.
Good. That's excellent news.
Say, um,
who is that Takashina guy exactly?
Takashina… My chauffeur?
Yes.
I mean, it's strange for a chauffeur
to also sit in on meetings.
I guess I was just curious.
She's got a point. It is unusual.
He has an interesting history, right?
It's fascinating.
Oh. Please.
Well, before Takashina worked for us,
he actually worked as a detective.
The truth is,
he even investigated our clinic
some time ago.
Oh.
Back when the chairman
still ran the practice,
he was accused
of allowing someone without qualifications
to administer anesthesia.
Takashina just wouldn't relent.
Yes, no matter what,
Takashina wouldn't give up,
which infuriated the chairman.
And then, one day,
he decided to use this in his favor.
The chairman realized
that if he could get Takashina
to work for him,
he'd use those skills
to protect the clinic.
There to take down anyone
who could be a threat.
Interesting.
Well?
How was the so-called new Hand of God?
Not too bad.
Still… nowhere close to the work done
on that cancer patient.
That was a true work of art.
So what, you wanna get back at her?
Well, now I know the truth.
I'm not staying quiet.
What are you thinking?
You've heard of the phrase
an eye for an eye, right?
Let's give her
a taste of her own medicine.
She's a cute little thing, isn't she?
She's certainly smart.
And very determined.
But still a bit fragile.
Should I… be worried
about her replacing me?
Don't be ridiculous, Lily.
Still… I'm glad
that you invited her over for dinner.
The tension in your fingers
is nothing like before.
The yips? Seriously?
Dr. Tohyama has that?
Of all people,
the Hand of God has the yips?
That's right. That's what happens
when you dub yourself the "Hand of God."
That's why she wanted to bring in
someone else to do her surgeries.
And that's the reason why I was recruited.
But is she okay with all of this?
With… doing all this work for no credit?
I told her I'm ready
to stop using an alias,
so she got the backlash started again.
There is no way around it.
I have to get her to do it.
I did hire her for this specific reason,
after all.
Thank you.
I'll take a shower.
What she wants is for me to stay hidden
on the dark side forever.
- You take card?
- Yeah, no problem.
- Thank you very much.
- There you go. Thanks.
Anyway, do your thing, and fast.
I'm good for it.
Thanks.
TAKERU NUMATA
CALL ME BACK NOW!
Here, you can put that back.
I'm so sorry.
It just happened.
Where were you?
I called you over and over.
I thought last night
that she was doing okay.
Thank you.
But why now?
We'd finally started
being able to talk to each other.
Why now?
Mom.
Mama.
Mom, Mom, Mom.
Mom!
Mom.
Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom.
Mama.
Mom!
Mom.
Mom. Mom.
I would still like to help you
however I can.
I will hear you out,
as a surgeon and without any judgment,
until you walk out of here
totally satisfied.
SPORTS DAY
So my thought was
to keep the funeral small, at home,
just us and our regulars.
Okay.
I think that's how
she would have wanted it.
Oh, and Fumi,
could you let your father know?
- Uh, my father?
- I think he deserves to know.
I don't think so,
and I don't even have his number.
Why don't you tell me his name,
and I'll find him?
- I dunno who he is.
- What?
Okay, well,
do you know what he does for work?
Uh, he's… probably a doctor.
- Whoa, for real?
- Oh, then we can for sure find him.
No, seriously, it's not worth it.
Look, Mom hadn't seen him in 30 years.
And anyway, she only mentioned once
he was a doctor.
And besides,
she… she was drunk when she said it.
Mom, what was my Dad like?
Your Dad?
Why are you asking about him?
It's past your bedtime anyway.
You see how late it is?
He's a quack doctor.
He was the absolute worst.
The absolute worst doctor.
- That's what she told you?
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, what if we look up
the absolute worst?
I said it's not worth it. Don't.
You know,
your father would be proud of you.
What?
Just that…
I mean,
you pursued the same career as him.
That's something, isn't it?
No, not really, no.
I also think it's interesting.
No, it's not. Leave it alone.
I'll be right back.
It is interesting.
SECRETS
In other news,
Governor Sakutaro Ohkura
has just announced
that he plans to run for a second term
in next month's election
for the governor of Tokyo.
My mission from the start
has been to improve Japan.
I've been working tirelessly
to transform Tokyo
into a thriving hub with global appeal.
Four years in office, however,
just hasn't been sufficient.
Hence this decision.
According to the latest polls,
half of your constituents are dissatisfied
with your performance thus far.
Why do you think that is?
If you look at it another way,
then the other half are satisfied,
are they not?
No one politician
is going to have a perfect rating.
But your ratings…
The governor is needed elsewhere.
Excuse us.
Sir, why the decline in ratings?
Wait, just one more!
Sir, one more question!
Sorry about the wait.
I see the battle has started.
Yes.
Please.
So, I would like to look
at least a decade younger.
You want to look ten years younger?
Yes, was I not clear?
If anyone can make that happen,
you can, Dr. Rin.
Quite honestly,
I never thought I'd hear that
from Tokyo's youngest governor ever.
That's fair.
As far as elected officials
and government leaders go,
I am indeed on the younger side.
That's precisely the problem
that Japan is currently facing.
Our political offices
are dominated by the elderly.
Hmm. Well, that's true.
So I want all that to change.
If I get reelected,
I plan to fill my cabinet with officials
in their twenties and thirties.
Just imagine seeing Tokyo run
by bright, youthful people,
full of hope and spirit.
That alone
will create a lasting impact.
Actually, I agree.
I think we'd better do what we can
to make you look young.
Great.
May I take a look at you?
Hmm.
I can certainly make you look younger,
but to make you look
as natural as possible,
then I would advise
combining the procedures.
It will take some time for you to recover,
and I assume
you'd like to be healed by the election.
So you'll want to get started right away?
That is ideal.
I'll just have to make time for you.
You were very instrumental
in helping me win the first time around.
However… I have one small condition.
What's that?
It involves that Beauty Hub project
you're working on.
Oh, yes, that. Your father said--
I would like you
to not use my father.
Not use him at all? Come on, Doctor--
Politics and plastic surgery
are not so different.
It also has a tendency…
to be exclusively run by the elderly.
That's true.
Yes, of course.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
Take as much time as you need
until you feel ready.
Thanks.
That being said,
I do have an important surgery
on the books.
I would like you to be there for it.
Right, but we haven't even planned
the funeral, and it might take a while.
Is it soon?
I realize
this is a difficult time for you,
but this patient
has to be ready by the election.
This is a crucial operation.
It could determine our future.
I'm asking you to think of the clinic.
I'm very sorry,
but I need you to be there.
You're quitting?
Whoa, Elsa, hang on.
You know Anna just quit last month.
We're short-staffed.
I'm not leaving you guys right away.
I'll still be on for a bit
once I'm healed.
Besides, I wanna say goodbye
to my clients.
What club is it? You found a place
that pays better, is that it?
No, that's not it.
I'm not getting any younger.
It's just time for me
to get my life on track.
What? What are you talking about?
Like, what have you done with Elsa?
Oh, come on. Shut up.
Well, the second you're healed,
you'll be itching for another surgery,
and you'll be back in no time, for sure.
Oh man. I can see that happening.
I know this game. I've seen it.
But I think I've finally found
a doctor I can really trust.
Oh, yeah?
Oh.
We're beginning the postmortem care,
so there's a few things
we'd like to check.
Our goal is to make her look
as much like herself as possible--
You know what?
If it's all right,
I'd like to do it myself.
Uh…
I have a rough idea of how to do it.
I wanna do it.
Hi, Mom.
Let's get started.
What?
How are you doing? Any pain?
I'm okay.
Great.
What is it?
Wait, slow down.
I'll be right there.
Do you have any idea
how much money I've given you guys?
I'm sorry.
Let me please check with my manager.
- Just one second.
- Sorry to have kept you waiting.
- I apologize.
- What's the problem?
What in the world is this, huh?
Is it true she has the yips?
What the hell is this?
The Hand of God doesn't get the yips.
She has the yips!
You can't let her work like this.
Tell us the truth. What's going on?
Mom? She got plastic surgery?
It was done a long time ago.
Takashi, you didn't know?
No. I thought she was all natural.
Maybe she was against plastic surgery
because she didn't like the way
hers was done.
- Yeah, that's it.
- I really doubt that.
Why's that?
Because her surgery was flawless.
Ah.
Oh, right.
I gotta find a photo of her.
I'm supposed to give them one tomorrow.
Takeru, do you have one?
Sorry.
Mom would always do weird faces in photos.
- Oh, yeah, she did.
- Fumi?
Me?
Never thought to take a picture of her.
What about
when she was a hostess in Ginza?
Or we can find one
from before her surgery.
- That would be nice.
- Right?
- You think one exists?
- Maybe.
But it could.
- Where?
- I bet we can find one.
Shouldn't we put out
an official statement?
No.
We cannot substantiate
baseless rumors like these.
I mean, if we give it weight,
the media will jump right on it.
And if we do nothing,
we might lose business.
We let it blow over.
We'll explain to our clients
that this is nothing more
than Internet gossip.
Trust me, the worst thing to do
would be to issue an official response.
Once we do, we legitimize it.
We're saying it's worth commenting on.
Oh, and also, the PR team
and your media department
should pivot to damage control.
Have we identified the source?
I know who started it.
Who?
I saw the chairman not long ago.
He was with Sara.
- You think he could have done this?
- Well, that can't be it.
The chairman
would never do something this egregious.
It could destroy everything he's built.
If he didn't,
then find out who did.
- Hey, hey, hey, get in here.
- Whoa.
Ms. Todoroki, did you know?
- What?
- About her yips.
I refuse to talk about
such silly little rumors.
Knock it off.
We all know you've been on her side
this whole time, Ms. Todoroki.
Don't play dumb. You must have known.
Hey, everyone.
- Hello.
- What's up? How come you're all here?
We're discussing something important.
Yeah? You heard about her yips too,
I guess?
Huh?
Mr. Hikita, do you know something?
What is it?
- Hmm.
- You think he…
- He knows something.
- Yeah.
- Of course.
- He knows for sure.
Listen.
This is all just a dumb rumor.
There's absolutely no proof behind it.
You know how skilled the director is,
don't you, Dr. Rui?
Mm. Of course I do.
Still, though, if this were true,
it would explain a lot of things lately.
Hmm, like why she would bring on
someone new.
Someone like Numata.
Oh, I've been wondering that too.
- Right?
- Yeah, totally.
Hmm.
What about this?
Eh, I'm sure we can find something better.
You know, I can't find
any pictures of your entrance ceremony.
I remember taking some.
- We did, right?
- Weird, I wonder where they are.
By the way, is everything okay
over at the clinic?
Why?
I saw some random post
about a "ghost doctor."
Don't worry.
Doesn't concern us.
- Whoa! What? This is crazy!
- Oh my goodness.
What in the world?
- Maybe they found one.
- I guess.
Come on. Let's go see.
Whoa, look at this!
- You find one?
- Can you believe it?
Whoa!
What?
Your mom was hiding this.
Hiding what?
A stash.
Seriously? Don't shout
if you didn't find a photo.
There's a hundred million yen here!
Wait, what?
Huh?
Let me see that.
Hundred, a thousand,
ten thousand, hundred thousand,
a million, ten million, a hundred million.
- Did you know about this at all?
- No.
Mommy wasn't ever able
to save up money like this.
So Mom forgot about it too?
No, this amount of money,
the bank would contact her
to make sure
the account wouldn't just become dormant.
- And how do you know this?
- Well, I used to work in finance.
- Huh.
- Hang on a second.
The whole time
we were trying to figure out
how to pay back your debt, Mom had this?
I've been working at the clinic
for nothing?
That lying witch!
Hey, be careful! Calm down!
It's okay.
CLINIC CLOSED TODAY
Sorry to make you come in on your day off.
Not at all.
My pleasure.
The bank said
that the full hundred million
is still all there.
It was transferred over by… Taro Yamada?
Doesn't sound real.
Yeah, that's definitely a made-up name.
Maybe it's dirty money.
Huh.
Even if it is, it's been almost 30 years.
It's well past the statute of limitations.
Once the inheritance is finalized,
the money is yours to share.
Hmm.
Fumi.
Takeru and I were discussing,
and we decided we want you
to have our shares of the money.
What, are you crazy?
But there's strings attached.
Use it to pay off Tohyama.
I think we could cover the remainder
if we all pitch in.
Anyway, Mommy would want you
to stop working as a plastic surgeon
as quickly as possible, don't you think?
So here.
We are aware this is very sudden,
but our schedule has changed.
So the surgery must be done tomorrow.
Uh, sorry?
It's the only slot we have.
The governor will be attending
a fundraiser tomorrow afternoon.
He'll come straight here after.
Uh… I have no problem with that.
Just know that
to give you the results you're hoping for,
we'll need to perform
all of these procedures.
Recovery will take
a minimum of three weeks.
And in some cases, it takes even longer.
Are you okay with that possibility?
The day after the fundraiser,
the governor
will announce an extended hospital stay.
Extended?
You may know this already,
but I battled cancer
when I was just out of law school.
Oh. Yes, it… it was thyroid cancer,
wasn't it?
So you're going to say
that it's come back?
I'll say that it was caught early,
and that I'll still do radiation
out of caution.
This way, we're able to explain
a three-week leave from work.
Fortunately, the election campaign
also begins in three weeks.
Yes, but wouldn't announcing
you have cancer
cause your campaign to be at risk?
The election team said the same thing.
I'm of the opinion,
pinning it on an illness
will allow me
to get liposuction too, right?
Well, then.
Damage control? Already?
That's right. They're mobilizing
their PR and media departments.
TOHYAMA YIPS
WHERE DID YOU HEAR
THAT DR. TOHYAMA HAS THE YIPS?
PROBABLY SOME RIVAL CLINIC'S DOING.
MY FACE IS ALL THE PROOF YOU NEED.
The clinic's hired influencers
are out in full force.
Have you heard of
the voice actress Mashiro Himenoki?
Yeah.
I have. Why?
Well, she just announced
that she had plastic surgery.
She just posted this video.
It's really blowing up.
I'm so angry right now.
And I'm sad, too, to hear these rumors.
Dr. Rin is amazing.
How could she have done my surgeries…
Can you get a hold of anything
that would prove that she has the yips?
She made it better.
It's not exactly that simple.
We gotta provide something,
or this will blow over
as just more fake news.
Well, I can see if there's a record
of that one case at the clinic somewhere.
The blind girl?
Yeah.
Her.
I'll look into it.
Okay, good luck.
Let's go, Okayu.
Mm.
Here we go.
Okay.
What the hell?
RECOMMENDED FOR GIFTS
I'll take this.
Sure.
- Is it for yourself?
- No, it's a gift.
Ah.
My son. It's his birthday today.
Ah, how lovely.
Can I add a card to it?
Yes, of course.
We have three options.
Ah.
SARA KONOIKE
ENTER PASSWORD TO OPEN "RECORDS"
Why would you do this?
And you better tell the truth.
Why?
Why in the world would you spread
such horrible lies like this?
I'm not sure they are lies.
There is no evidence,
medical or otherwise,
that I have the yips.
Then explain
why you need help with your surgeries.
And besides…
…who's spreading horrible lies, really?
What do you mean?
Oh, please, Doctor.
Who's the one who hired a former detective
to spread dirt about me online, huh?
I found out everything.
Well.
- What do you want?
- I'm getting out of here.
Obviously.
Now that I know what you are,
there's no way I'm gonna stay here.
Why don't you cut out the theatrics?
- Where are you going?
- You listen.
I have enough information
to close your clinic for good if I want.
Like how you approved breast augmentation
on someone with a tumor.
Or how you made a girl go blind.
Everything.
Not to mention
you can't even properly operate
on your own.
And who exactly do you think
will listen to you, Dr. Backlash?
Now who's the real Dr. Backlash?
- Wow, it's really pouring.
- Hello.
It's like a monsoon.
- Definitely.
- It really is.
Hello.
FUNERAL SERVICE FOR TAEKO NUMATA
It's gonna be okay.
What should we do?
I don't know what to do.
My condolences.
You should take the car, ma'am.
I'll be fine.
I need to clear my head.
Are you sure?
About Dr. Numata,
let me handle it tomorrow.
All right.
- Good night.
Takeru, can you go get some more snacks?
- Where?
- Uh, under the counter.
I think, uh, right where
your mother's chair was.
Okay, okay.
Another!
Bring the good stuff!
- And more sushi.
- Any of that dip?
Yeah. Yeah, I'll do a shot of beer.
Don't you have a tray somewhere here?
- No way.
- What? Who ate it?
I can take over.
You should go eat something.
No.
Don't have an appetite.
Even so, you've got a busy day tomorrow.
There's the bottle.
Fumi?
Strange how…
how we can never really go back.
What?
I might take a beer after all.
Sure thing.
Here.
Allow me.
Ah. Ah.
- There, that's good.
- Okay.
Thanks.
Not bad.
- Thank you.
- No. It's nothing.
- Thanks.
- Of course.
Fumi, I found a picture under the counter.
An old one of Mom?
Mm.
Isn't this from when she was
the top-ranked hostess in Ginza?
Wow, so young!
Fumi, is that you in her arms?
- Guess so.
- Most likely.
Wait, look.
This photo was cut in half.
Oh yeah, it was.
So the other half of the photo must be of…
Gotta be your father.
Put it back.
Someone's just arrived. Right this way.
- I'll get rid of these.
- Okay.
- Put that back where you found it.
- Go ahead. Light a candle.
- You see who that is?
- Isn't that…
I am so sorry… about your mother.
I mean it.
It was truly the work of my successor.
You can't even properly operate
on your own.
"Arata Tohyama." Wow. It really was him.
Hmm. Makes sense he'd come.
He's her boss, after all.
Mm, yeah. True that.
Here.
My goodness!
Right? Incredible.
How much is in here?
- Whoa.
- What?
- That's crazy.
There he is.
Rin, come look.
The chairman is holding
a press conference.
Thank you for coming
to this press conference…
I got caught in the rain.
I'm gonna shower.
Hello, everyone.
I, Arata Tohyama, plan to return
to practicing cosmetic surgery
within the year.
Many clinics seem to grow larger each day.
I've decided to go against the grain
and will create an exclusive,
one-of-a-kind clinic.
While I would have liked for my daughter,
my successor,
to be the head of this new clinic,
unfortunately, this will not be the case.
Therefore, I will instead be training
a new successor
as the next "Hand of God."
There is a rumor that the current director
is using a ghost doctor for her surgeries.
I don't concern myself
with petty little rumors like that.
That being said,
they can have a kernel of truth.
I look forward to hearing
what the director has to say
regarding the matter.
Chairman Tohyama,
what will be the name of your new clinic?
I founded
the Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic.
I gave it a strong name.
It's one that I have always cherished.
So I shall open the clinic
under that name.
Of course, there can't be two clinics
with the same name.
It would confuse our clients.
Therefore, I shall request
that the other clinic change its name.
SPORTS DAY
Oh, hi, Rin! It's been a while.
Indeed, it has.
Go on in.
Thank you.
We've been expecting you, Ms. Itai.
Right this way.
This procedure
must stay completely confidential.
A leak could jeopardize the election.
So make sure
you don't share with the staff either.
The only ones
who can know about this are us
and our anesthesiologist, Dr. Taki.
So it will be done
under general anesthesia?
- What?
- But no assisting doctor?
No, the director
will do the surgery unassisted.
Unassisted?
How could you be so devious?
Devious?
Yeah. You don't think
I'm capable anymore, right?
Then just say it to my face.
Using a press conference
is a pathetic thing for a father to do.
I've sent you a lot of signals
to that effect, Rin,
but you've been clearly
disregarding my concerns.
Am I wrong?
So who's truly devious, then?
Don't pretend otherwise.
And if I were your actual child?
Is it 'cause you adopted me
that you can act so cruelly?
Adopted or not,
it makes no difference.
I've been very clear.
I bear the Tohyama name.
I own the clinic bearing that name,
and you are
a disappointment, Rin.
You can go off
and start your own practice,
but I have the right
to do as I see fit with mine.
It will be down to the clients
to determine which surgeon
has the most talent.
Thank you for waiting.
We'll remove your stitches today.
Oh, of course. Forgive me.
I'm Komiya.
I'll be your doctor from here on out.
But Dr. Numata…
Ah, yes. Allow me to explain.
I'm afraid
that Dr. Numata has left our practice.
Wait.
Ms. Itai!
Ms. Itai has left without paying.
She says she'll only be treated by Numata.
So I told her
that she should talk to her directly
and that her address was leaked online.
Yeah, but she didn't settle anything.
Small price to get rid of her
once and for all.
GOVERNOR OHKURA
Governor, good morning. Everything okay?
Dr. Rin.
Here's the thing.
I hate to do this so last minute,
but… the team here has decided
not to proceed with my surgery.
My campaign manager saw
the chairman's press conference,
and he changed his mind about it.
So, I thought
I should simply ask you directly, Dr. Rin.
Oh? Ask what?
Well, ask if…
you're someone I can trust?
Governor,
you can have complete confidence
in my abilities.
You can trust me fully.
Good, I'm glad.
Then let's do it.
Great.
Ms. Itai.
Ms. Itai, your stitches!
You lied.
You're a liar!
I'm sorry.
How could you say all those things?
You actually made me believe
that you weren't like all the rest!
- I'm so sorry.
- Get off! Don't you touch me!
I actually trusted you.
I won't forgive you.
I will never forgive you!
I'm so sorry. Ms. Itai…
This is it.
I like it.
It's far more modern than Ginza.
Thank you very much.
This area is a prime location.
There's only a select few
available within Roppongi,
and they're going fast.
It's perfect.
I'd like to take it.
Fabulous.
Okay, so what do you want?
This right here…
is what you've been looking for.
TEST RESULTS
KANA KOKUBUN
SARA KONOIKE
What? Why?
Because this line of work
is full of secrets, isn't it?
I told lie after lie
just to contain it all.
Maybe
I was doing too much.
I'm ready now.
I've got nothing left to protect.
You mean you're quitting?
One more thing.
If your intention is
to make these documents public,
I just ask that you wait
until after the election.
You might think it strange,
but I'd like him to win.
I think he'd do well.
I think
the chairman is hoping you'll do that.
Look,
I know your family is none of my business.
Even so, I can't believe your own father
would say something like that.
He's…
He is not my real father.
What?
I just wanted him
to love me anyway.
I've desperately sought his approval.
Thank you for all you've done.
I can finally let go.
SNACK BAR ITTENBARI
I'VE SET IT UP SO YOU CAN SEE TOMOKI
AFTER SPORTS DAY.
WAIT SOMEWHERE ELSE UNTIL THEN.
Excuse me, Dr. Rin.
Do you have a moment?
What is it?
Well,
as this clinic's vice director,
I think I deserve an explanation
about all these rumors,
not to mention
the chairman's press conference.
Tomorrow.
What?
I will explain everything tomorrow.
Yeah, you got this! Go! Go! Run!
Come on! Go! Run!
Yeah! Go! You've got this!
Go! Go! Run! Come on! Yeah!
Run! Run! Run! Yeah! You've got this!
Run! Go faster! Go! Go!
Go even faster! Go! Run! Run! Run! Go!
I loved just how happy you always were.
Thank you, Mom.
I'm so grateful that I got to meet you.
Mama.
You can rest now.
I love you.
I'LL SEND HIM YOUR WAY NOW.
Director? The governor is here.
Ms. Todoroki.
Yes?
Should something go wrong…
I trust your judgment
to pull the plug on the procedure.
Of course, ma'am.
He is a quack doctor.
He was the absolute worst.
I was worried
that even after all these years,
she still wasn't over it.
Maybe that's why
she ended up an alcoholic.
Seriously, just lay off and let me drink.
That's why he left. It's all my fault.
He left me with Fumi.
It's gonna be okay. It's fine.
It's okay.
He is not my real father.
You've got great fingers for surgery.
If only we were all so lucky.
Just relax.
Okay.
- Administering anesthesia.
- Okay.
Right.
All right.
Let's begin.
- Scalpel.
- Yes, Doctor.
Director, stop.
Taking over. Five minutes.
I'll assist you.
Why?
It's not because I want to help you.
It's just
I can't see that man win.
I won't let it happen. Not on my watch.
He doesn't deserve it.
- Right. Starting other side.
- Right.
Swapping sides.
It's your call.
I'll take over.
Mm.
- I'll assist.
- All right.
He's not my real father.
- Controlling the bleeding.
- Thank you.
You've got great fingers for surgery.
You did well today.
Thanks to you,
he's got this election
pretty much locked in.
Since when are elections based on looks?
Well, since forever. You didn't know?
Uh, no, I suppose I didn't.
I've decided to fight.
I won't roll over.
We can take him on, the two of us.
As a pair, we're unstoppable.
I can take on my father.
I know I can.
What made you decide
to return to the clinic?
You said
he didn't deserve to win.
Well, uh…
To be honest,
I think my family is like yours.
- They pity you?
- No, not that.
It's…
I mean, I…
I can't stand it when kids are forced
to take on a burden that isn't theirs.
I won't help him push you down.
And I see how you've been struggling.
And it's been quite the show.
Mm.
Thank you.
My insecurities
have caused you
so much pain.
I hope you can accept my apology.
And trust me.
I will make it up to you.
I hope…
…you'll stay at the clinic.
Mm.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
Everyone's here.
Yeah, looks that way.
I must remove your stitches.
Please let me do that.
Right this way.
This room.
I've been expecting you.